Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Charters Collections, 1899-2014 IBT0087
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- IBT Local Charters, 1899-2014; Series 1
  - Local 600, Highway, City, and Air Freight Drivers, Dockmen, Marine Officers Association and Helpers, St. Louis, Missouri, June 10, 1986 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Local 600, Highway, City, and Air Freight Drivers, Dockmen, Marine Officers Association and Helpers, St. Louis, Missouri, February 27, 1990 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - Local 603, Milk Wagon Drivers, Inside Dairy Workers, Ice Cream Drivers, Ice Cream Production, Butter and Creamery Employees, Clerical Employees, and Allied Food Workers, St. Louis and Surrounding Counties, Missouri, July 31, 1964 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - Local 608, United Parcel Pilots, Air Maintenance, and Related Classifications, The United States and Possessions, October 21, 1987 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - Local 614, Teamsters, Pontiac, Michigan, December 1, 1940 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - Local 617, Truck Drivers, Jersey City, New Jersey, December 13, 1950 (Box 5, Item 6)
  - Local 617, Truck Drivers, Warehousemen, Frozen Foods, and Allied Industries of Northern New Jersey, January 26, 1993 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - Local 624, General Truck Drivers, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Marin, Sonoma, and Lake Counties, California, March 12, 1986 (Box 5, Item 8)
  - Local 639, Drivers, Dairy, Law Enforcement, Public Employees, Healthcare Workers, and Housekeeping and Laundry Aides, Washington, DC, July 15, 2009 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - Local 649, Teamsters, Jamestown, Olean, and Vicinity, New Jersey, November 19, 1985 (Box 5, Item 10)
  - Local 650, Teamsters, Waterloo, Iowa, October 9, 1934 (Box 5, Item 11)
  - Local 650, Teamsters, Waterloo, Iowa, February 25, 2004 (Box 5, Item 12)
  - Local 654, Teamsters, Champaign, Clark, Darke, Greene, Miami, Montgomery, and Preble Counties, Ohio, February 5, 1973 (Box 5, Item 13)
  - Local 661, Warehouse, Production, and Maintenance Employees and Furniture, Piano, Express Drivers and Helpers, Ohio and Kentucky, August 20, 1971 (Box 5, Item 14)
  - Local 662, Teamsters, Wisconsin, May 24, 1978 (Box 5, Item 15)
  - Local 657, Teamsters, Texas, February 18, 1997 (Box 5, Item 1)
  - Local 665,Teamsters Automotive Workers, San Francisco, California, July 12, 1965 (Box 5, Item 2)
  - Local 665, Teamsters Automotive Workers, San Francisco, California, January 6, 2006 (Box 5, Item 3)
  - Local 669, Bakery, Laundry, Beverage Drivers, and Vending Machine Servicemen, Albany, New York, April 11, 1957 (Box 5, Item 4)
  - Local 670, Teamsters, Salem, Oregon, April 14, 1986 (Box 5, Item 5)
  - Local 673, Teamsters, Wheaton County, Illinois, December 1, 1940 (Box 5, Item 6)
  - Local 676, Teamsters, Camden, South Jersey Areas, New Jersey, May 19, 1964 (Box 5, Item 7)
  - Local 682, Construction, Building Material, Ice and Coal, Laundry and Dry Cleaning, Meat and Food Products Drivers, St. Louis, Missouri, July 12, 1983 (Box 5, Item 8)
  - Local 688, Teamsters, Missouri and Illinois, March 16, 1981 (Box 5, Item 9)
  - Local 692, General Truck Drivers, Chauffeurs, and Helpers, Long Beach, Wilmington, San Pedro, California, October 26, 1965 (Box 5, Item 10)
  - Local 693, Teamsters, Binghamton, New York, April 21, 1976 (Box 5, Item 11)
  - Local 695, Drivers, Salesmen, Warehousemen, Milk Processors, Cannery, Dairy Employees, Wisconsin, March 26, 1984 (Box 5, Item 12)
  - Local 703, Produce, Fresh and Frozen and Vegetables, Fish, Egss, Butter, Cheese, Poultry, Florist, Nursery, Landscape, Warehousemen and Helpers, Chicago and Vicinity, Illinois, December 1, 1960 (Box 5, Item 13)
  - Local 707, Highway and Local Motor Freight Drivers, Dockmen, and Helpers, New York, New York, June 22, 1950 (Box 5, Item 14)
  - Local 711, Teamsters, British Columbia, October 11, 1988 (Box 5, Item 15)
  - Local 712, Laundry, Dyers, Chauffeurs, Helpers, Chicago, Illinois, March 29, 1946 (Box 5, Item 16)
  - Local 714, Machinery, Scrap Iron, Metal and Steel, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, Handlers, Helpers, Alloy Fabrications, Public Employees, Pharmacists, Motion Picture, Theatrical, Exposition, Convention and Trade Show Exmployees, Chicago, Illinois, January 27, 2000 (Box 5, Item 17)
  - Local 716, Coal, Ice, Building Material, Supply Drivers, Indianapolis, Indiana, January 18, 1950 (Box 5, Item 18)
  - Local 719, Warehousing Distributing and Processing Employees, New York, New York, November 24, 1965 (Box 5, Item 19)
  - Local 722, General Truck Drivers, Dockmen, Helpers, Warehousement, Sales Drivers, Automotive Workers, Gas Station Attendants, La Salle, Putnam, and Bureau Counties, Illinois, December 4, 1956 (Box 5, Item 20)
  - Local 725, Armored Car Drivers, Helpers, Messengers, and Allied Employees, Chicago, Illinois, October 21, 1958 (Box 5, Item 21)
  - Local 740, Corrections, Law Enforcement, Safety Employees, Ohio, April 1, 1984 (Box 5, Item 22)
  - Local 743, Warehouse, Mail Order, Office, Technical and Professional Employees, Chcago, Illinois, May 30, 1974 (Box 5, Item 23)
  - Local 747, Professional Flight Deck Crew Members Worldwide, September 25, 1995 (Box 5, Item 24)
  - Local 749, Teamsters, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, June 21, 1937 (Box 5, Item 25)
  - Local 749, Teamsters, Sioux Falls, North Dakota, August 21, 1941 (Box 5, Item 26)
  - Local 757, Teamsters, New York, New York, November 10, 1940 (Box 5, Item 27)
  - Local 761, Notions, Candies, Tobacco and Cigarette Salesmen, Drivers, Helpers, and Inside Workers, Chicago, Illinois, October 26, 1964 (Box 5, Item 28)
  - Local 769, Teamsters, Miami and Vicinity, Florida, April 27, 1966 (Box 5, Item 29)
  - Local 777, Laborers, Unskilled and Miscellaneous Workers, Chicago, Illinois, February 25, 1975 (Box 5, Item 30)
  - Local 783, Teamsters, Louisville, Kentucky, April 29, 1965 (Box 5, Item 31)
  - Local 786, Building Material, Lumber, Box, Shaving, Roofing, Teamsters, Warehousemen and Helpers, Related Industry Employees, Chicago, Illinois, February 24, 1997 (Box 5, Item 32)
  - Local 789, Teamsters, West Virginia, January 28, 1965 (Box 5, Item 33)
  - Local 798, Plastic and Textile Printing Workers, Plainfield and Norwich, Connecticut, October 1, 1969 (Box 5, Item 34)
  - Local 802, Bakery Drivers, New York, New York, December 20, 1963 (Box 5, Item 35)
  - Local 803, Professional, Technical, Clerical and Ancillary, Employees, Greater Metropolitan Area of New York, November 25, 2003 (Box 5, Item 36)
  - Local 806, Teamsters, New York, New York, September 1, 1966 (Box 5, Item 37)
  - Local 807, Truck Drivers, New York, New York, December 1, 1940 (Box 5, Item 38)
  - Local 812, Soft Drink Workers Union, New York, New York, May 19, 1942 (Box 5, Item 39)
  - Local 812, Soft Drinks, Brewery Workers, and Delivery Employees, Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees, Greater New York, October 27, 1998 (Box 5, Item 40)
  - Local 813, Private Sanitation, Resource Recovery and Transfer and Recycling Station Employees, New York, May 4, 1987 (Box 5, Item 41)
  - Local 813, Private Sanitation, Resource Recovery and Transfer and Recycling Station Employees, New York, July 3, 1996 (Box 5, Item 42)
  - Local 815, Drug, Chemical, Cosmetic Plastics and Affiliated Industries Warehouse Employees, New York, August 1, 1952 (Box 5, Item 43)
  - Local 819, Merchandising and Allied Products, Textile Household Products, and Industrial and Allied Trade Workers, New York, June 12, 2002 (Box 5, Item 44)
  - Local 827, Industrial Workersm Warehousemen, Drivers, and Helpers, St. Paul, Minnesota, May 5, 1966 (Box 5, Item 45)
  - Local 828, Teamsters, Iowa, October 11, 1984 (Box 5, Item 46)
  - Local 829, Teamsters, Boston, Massachusetts, March 18, 1943 (Box 5, Item 47)
  - Local 839, Teamsters, Southeastern Washington, March 16, 1981 (Box 5, Item 48)
  - Local 840, Technical, Industrial, Service Agency and Allied Workers, New York, May 24, 1996 (Box 5, Item 49)
  - Local 853, Teamsters, California, July 29, 1999 (Box 5, Item 50)
  - Local 854, Television, Radio, Instrument, Business Machine and Furniture Manufacturing, New York, January 28, 1959 (Box 5, Item 51)
  - Local 857, Cannery Workers and Warehousemen, California, June 29, 1998 (Box 5, Item 52)
  - Local 858, Off Track Betting, Professional, Clerical and Wagering Employees, New York, April 1, 1980 (Box 5, Item 53)
  - Local 860, Teamsters, San Francisco, California, May 8, 1975 (Box 5, Item 54)
  - Local 864, Teamsters, Rolla, Missouri, September 6, 1944 (Box 5, Item 55)
  - Local 868, Automobile and Truck Salesmen, and Clerical Sales Employees, All Employees in Express Trucking, New York, November 14, 1989 (Box 5, Item 56)
  - Local 872, Teamsters, Charleroi, Pennsylvania, September 27, 1937 (Box 5, Item 57)
  - Local 875, Rug Cleaners, Dyers. Handlers, Drivers, Helpers, and Production Workers, New York, March 15, 1954 (Box 5, Item 58)
  - Local 887, Municipal Employees Union, New York, April 18, 1986 (Box 5, Item 59)
  - Local 892, General Warehusemen and Allied Industries Employees, New Jersey, February 27, 1985 (Box 5, Item 60)
  - Local 903, Construction and Supply Drivers, Construction and Supply Drivers of Montreal and Gas Station and Parking Attendants of Quebec, January 9, 1975 (Box 6, Item 1)
  - Local 911, California Teamsters Public Professional and Medical Employees Union, California excluding San Francisco, Santa Clara, Contra Costa, Alameda, San Mateo, and Marin Counties, August 1, 1975 (Box 6, Item 2)
  - Local 917, Automobile Mechanics and Helpers, Gasoline Station and Parking Attendants, Automotive Transporters and Inland Warehousemen, New York Metropolitan Area, May 4, 1977 (Box 6, Item 3)
  - Local 926, Automotive, Chauffeurs, Ports and Garage Employees, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, January 15, 1945 (Box 6, Item 4)
  - Local 926, Teamsters Automotive Chauffeurs, Parts, Garage, and Airline Employees, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, March 26, 2001 (Box 6, Item 5)
  - Local 931, Cartage and Miscellaneous Employees Union, Montreal Island and radius of 150 miles, September 10, 1981 (Box 6, Item 6)
  - Local 955, Department Store, Package, Grocery, Paper House, Liquor, Meat Drivers, Warehousemen, Bakery, Dry Cleaning, Laundry and Miscellaneous Sales Routemen and Helpers, Kansas City, Missouri, October 30, 1997 (Box 6, Item 7)
  - Local 957, Teamsters, Dayton, Ohio, September 15, 1941 (Box 6, Item 8)
  - Local 961, Line Drivers and Airline, Freight Lines, Automotive and Racetrack Employees, Colorado, July 25, 1968 (Box 6, Item 9)
  - Local 961, Line Drivers and Airline, Freight Lines, Automotive and Racetrack Employees, Newspaper, Pressman, Plate Makers, Pre-Press, Drivers, Loaders and Dispatchers, Colorado, March 8, 2010 (Box 6, Item 10)
  - Local 963, Teamsters, Bradford, Pennsylvania, June 8, 1943 (Box 6, Item 11)
  - Local 969, Teamsters, Lake Charles, Pennsylvania, April 8, 1942 (Box 6, Item 12)
  - Local 970, Metal Shop Warehousemen and Helpers, Minneapolis and St. Paul, Minnesota, June 3, 1957 (Box 6, Item 13)
  - Local 976, Teamsters, Ogden, Utah, June 2, 1954 (Box 6, Item 14)
  - Local 990, Teamsters, Northwest Ontario, September 19, 1968 (Box 6, Item 15)
  - Local 997, Brewery Workers and Soft Drink Employees, Fort Worth, Texas, May 2, 1988 (Box 6, Item 16)
  - Local 999, Metal Plastics, Novelty, and Production Workers, Passaic and Bergen Counties, New Jersey, August 5, 1959 (Box 6, Item 17)
  - Local 1001, Boston Mailers, Boston, Massachusetts, March 12, 1987 (Box 6, Item 18)
  - Local 1010, Brewery Workers, Maryland, December 5, 1973 (Box 6, Item 19)
  - Local 1010, Brewery Workers, Maryland, January 28, 1985 (Box 6, Item 20)
  - Local 1034, Chauffeurs and Helpers, Container, Drum, Miscellaneous Workers, Funeral, Livery, Rentals, Poultry, Casket, and Vault Employees, New York Metropolitan Area, March 17, 1970 (Box 6, Item 21)
  - Local 1038, Brewery Drivers, Helpers, and Dockmen, Detroit, Michigan, November 16, 1973 (Box 6, Item 22)
  - Local 1040, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Liquor Drivers, and New and Used Car Workers, Bridgeport, Connecticut, August 5, 1969 (Box 6, Item 23)
  - Local 1055, Kansas Mailers Union, Kansas, May 7, 1987 (Box 6, Item 24)
  - Local 1064, Teamsters Warehousemen and Factory Workers, Billings, Montana, April 14, 1954 (Box 6, Item 25)
  - Local 1067, Teamsters, Mitchell and Vicinity, Nebraska, December 1, 1980 (Box 6, Item 26)
  - Local 1068, Teamsters, Lovell, Wyoming, February 24, 1964 (Box 6, Item 27)
  - Local 1071, Teamsters, Scottsbluff, Nebraska, April 17, 1970 (Box 6, Item 28)
  - Local 1073, Teamsters, Bayard, Nebraska, September 16, 1966 (Box 6, Item 29)
  - Local 1081, Brewery Workers, La Crosse, Washington, November 21, 1973 (Box 6, Item 30)
  - Local 1108, Netjets Pilots and Affiliates, Worldwide, March 28, 2005 (Box 6, Item 31)
  - Local 1110, Brewery, Food, Construction, Communications, Disposal, Laundry, Warehousing, Delivery, Sales Drivers, Maintenance and Allied Employees, San Antonio and South and Central Texas, and Tulsa, Oklahoma, October 25, 1983 (Box 6, Item 32)
  - Local 1111, Brewery, Soft Drink, Industrial and Allied Workers, Baytown, Beaumont, Dallas, Fort Worth, Galveston, Houston, Nederland, Orange, Port Arthur, and Port Neches, Texas, November 20, 1973 (Box 6, Item 33)
  - Local 1135, Toledo Mailers Union, Northwest Ohio, December 2, 1987 (Box 6, Item 34)
  - Local 1137, Dayton Mailers Union, Ohio, September 8, 1987 (Box 6, Item 35)
  - Local 1149, Brewery Workers and Beer Distributors, Syracuse, New York, December 18, 1973 (Box 6, Item 36)
  - Local 1153, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Evansville, Indiana, December 3, 1973 (Box 6, Item 37)
  - Local 1196, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Memphis, Tennessee, November 16, 1973 (Box 6, Item 38)
  - Local 1196, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, Dairy, Public Employees, Woodworkers, and General Teamsters, Memphis, Tennessee, September 25, 1987 (Box 6, Item 39)
  - Local 1199, Bottle Beer Drivers, Beer and Soft Drink Bottlers and Allied Workers, Cincinnati, Ohio, November 16, 1973 (Box 6, Item 40)
  - Local 1224, Flight Deck Crew Members Employes by ABX Air, Inc, Wilmington, Ohio, January 18, 1994 (Box 6, Item 41)
  - Local 1247, Teamsters Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Item 42)
  - Local 1420, Teamsters Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Item 43)
  - Local 1518, Miscellaneous Employees, Northern New Jersey, November 2, 1971 (Box 6, Item 44)
  - Local 1603, Teamsters Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Item 45)
  - Local 1620, Commercial Mailers, Binders, and Related Workers, Plymouth, Michigan, April 23, 1987 (Box 6, Item 46)
  - Local 1688, Teamsters Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Item 47)
  - Local 1714, Correctional Officers and Employees, Washington, DC, March 25, 1987 (Box 6, Item 48)
  - Local 1791, Construction Industries and Miscellaneous Related Employees, Quebec, December 17, 2004 (Box 6, Item 49)
  - Local 1901, Teamsters Canada Correctional Officers Union, January 15, 2008 (Box 6, Item 50)
  - Local 1903, Teamsters Canada Correctional Officers Union, January 15, 2008 (Box 6, Item 51)
  - Local 1911, Ambulance Personnel, Quebec, June 16, 2004 (Box 6, Item 52)
  - Local 1969, Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Local 1996, Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, February 7, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Local 1998, Clothing, Apparel, Textile, Needle Trade and Related Industries, Quebec, January 20, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Local 2040, Detroit Mailers Union Local No, 40, Michigan, December 29, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Local 2040, Newspaper, Magazine, Electronic Media and Miscellaneous, Michigan, July 7, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Local 36, Building Material, Construction, Industrial, Professional, and Technical Teamsters, San Diego County, California, February 13, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Joint Council 44, Locals 20, 908, and 1135, Jurisdiction of its Affiliated Local Unions, December 23, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Local 113, Milk and Ice Cream Drivers and Dairy Employees, Canton, Ohio, December 1, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Local 138, Furniture, Flour, and Grocery Teamsters and Chauffeurs, Brooklyn, New York, December 1, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Local 153, Beer Drivers, Helpers, Unloaders, Platformmen, Yard Men, Sorters, Warehousemen, Fork Lift Operators, and Garage Employees, New Jersey, May 24, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Local 246, Dairy Delivery and Plant Processing, Bank, Appliance Service, Pharmacist, Public Law Enforcement Personnel and Related Clerical Employees, Washington, DC, February 5, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Local 680, Milk Drivers and Dairy Employees, Newark, New Jersey, December 1, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Local 802, Bakery, Pastry Drivers and Helpers (One Half of the Charter), July 13, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Local 819, Merchandising and Allied Products, Textile Household Products, New York, New York, August 2, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Local 918, Allied Chemical and Surgical Workers, New York Counties, October 28, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Local 937, Dairy, Soft Drink, Laundry, Linen, General Sales Drivers and Allied Employees, Baltimore, Maryland, November 30, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Local 213, Teamsters, British Columbia, Canada (2 small plaques), May 1, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Local 27, Paper Products and Miscellaneous Drivers, Warehousemen, Helpers and Messengers, New York, March 2, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Copy of local 395, Chauffers, Teamsters, and Helpers, Saskatchewan, Canada, December 13, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Local 531, Private Ambulance Drivers, New Jersey, November 4, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - opy of Local 723, Automobile Salesmen, Service, and Parts Personnel, New Jersey, December 1, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Local 802, Bakery and Pastry and Frozen Baked Products Drivers and Helpers, New York, November 5, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Local 901, Teamsters, Chauffers, and Helpers, Puerto Rico, July 12, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Local 964, Automobile Transporters, New Trailor, Armored Car Drivers, Mechanics, and Garagemen, Cleveland, Ohio, April 7, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Teamsters Canada Rail Conference and Maintenance of Way Employes Division, Canada, October 31, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- IBT Affiliate Charters, 1899-2014; Series 2
  This series contains charters from groups affiliated with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters.
  Items in this series are arranged chronologically.
  - Team Drivers International Union American Federation of Labor Duplicate Charter, January 27, 1899 (Box 7, Item 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters American Federation of Labor Charter, April 24, 1918 (Box 7, Item 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Building and Construction Trades Department of the American Federation of Labor Charter, April 2, 1941 (Box 7, Item 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Union Lable Trades Department American Federation of Labor Affiliation, May 6, 1941 (Box 7, Item 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters American Federation of Labor Charter, January 3, 1941 (Box 7, Item 5)
  - Joint Council 42, Los Angeles, California, March 6, 1942 (Box 7, Item 6)
  - United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America Congress of Industrial Organizations Charter, July 1, 1946 (Box 7, Item 7)
  - Illinois Conference of Teamsters Charter, December 1, 1948 (Box 7, Item 8)
  - Joint Council 90, Alberta and Saskatchewan, October 9, 1958 (Box 7, Item 9)
  - International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink, and Distillery Workers AFL-CIO Charter, December 7, 1955 (Box 7, Item 10)
  - International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America Union Label and Service Trades Department, AFL-CIO Charter, February 1, 1957 (Box 7, Item 11)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Metal Trades Department, AFL-CIO Charter, January 1, 1957 (Box 7, Item 12)
  - Kentucky-West Virginia Conference of Teamsters, October 28, 1965 (Box 7, Item 13)
  - IBT American Communications Association- Communication Trade Division, United States and Canada Charter, November 16, 1966 (Box 7, Item 14)
  - Central Conference of Teamsters, May 12, 1978 (Box 7, Item 15)
  - Southern Conference of Teamsters, May 12, 1978 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Western Conference of Teamsters, May 12, 1978 (Box 7, Item 17)
  - Eastern Conference of Teamsters, May 12, 1978 (Box 7, Item 18)
  - Bakery Conference, December 29, 1978 (Box 7, Item 19)
  - Joint Council 3, Colorado, Wyoming, Arizona, and New Mexico, June 7, 1978 (Box 7, Item 20)
  - Joint Council 79, Chemical, Energy, and Allied Workers, Ontario, May 7, 1979 (Box 7, Item 21)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Public Employee Department, AFL-CIO Charter, February 1, 1988 (Box 7, Item 22)
  - Joint Council 1, Jurisdiction of Affiliated Local Unions, January 22, 1996 (Box 7, Item 23)
  - Joint Council 3, Colorado, Wyoming, New Mexico, Montana, Utah, Southern Idaho, Nebraska, May 24, 1996 (Box 7, Item 24)
  - Joint Council 84, West Virginia, January 14, 1997 (Box 7, Item 25)
  - Teamsters Canada Rail Conference, October 31, 2003 (Box 7, Item 26)
  - Teamsters Canada Rail Conference, October 31, 2003 (Box 7, Item 27)
  - Indiana Conference of Teamsters, State of Indiana, December 16, 1948 (Box 7, Item 28)